Home is a war away
Sand Castle is a war, action, drama film directed by Fernando Coimbra.
Set during the occupation of Iraq, a squad of U.S.
soldiers try to protect a small village.
Matt Ocre, played by Nicholas Hoult.
Sergeant Harper, played by Logan Marshall-Green.
Captain Syverson, played by Henry Cavill.
Haring, played by Gonzalo Menendez.
Sergeant Burton, played by Beau Knapp.
1st LT Anthony, played by Sam Spruell.
Sand Castle is a 2017 American war drama film directed by
Fernando Coimbra and written by Chris Roessner.
The film stars Nicholas Hoult, Logan Marshall-Green, Henry Cavill, Glen
Powell, Tommy Flanagan, Beau Knapp, and Neil Brown Jr.
The film centers on Matt Ocre, a young soldier in the United States Army,
who is tasked with restoring water to a village in Iraq.
It is inspired by Roessner's experience as a soldier in the Iraq War.
It was released on April 21, 2017, on Netflix.
The film explores themes of iraq, small village, occupation, american soldiers.
The tone is emotional.